People often wonder why some entrepreneurs have greater success than others.
人们常常想知道，为什么有些创业者比别人更成功。
Is it habits, connections, luck, work ethic or some other factor?
是习惯、人脉、运气、敬业精神，还是其他某种因素？
I believe the key to success is willpower.
我认为成功的关键在于意志力。
Willpower is the ability to control yourself.
意志力是控制自己的能力。
It is a strong determination that allows you to do something difficult.
它是一种坚定的决心，能让你去做困难的事情。
It is a behavior we are born with more than one we learn; however, it is possible to not only learn it, but also strengthen it with constant exercise.
它更多是一种与生俱来的行为，而不是后天学会的行为；不过，我们不仅可以学会它，还可以通过不断锻炼来增强它。
Willpower is just like a muscle; to keep it strong you need to constantly exercise it.
意志力就像肌肉一样；要让它保持强健，你需要不断地锻炼它。
People with a great amount of willpower have the discipline to develop positive, successful habits.
意志力充沛的人有足够的自律来养成积极的、能带来成功的习惯。
Even with an incredible amount of talent, without the discipline and motivation to create positive habits, it can be difficult to achieve success.
即使天赋惊人，如果缺乏养成积极习惯所需的自律和动力，也可能很难取得成功。
Willpower and habits go hand in hand.
意志力与习惯相辅相成。
It is critical to create good habits and take the actions necessary to stick to those habits day in and day out for greater success.
要取得更大的成功，至关重要的是养成良好的习惯，并采取必要的行动，日复一日地坚持这些习惯。
Almost half of our daily actions are part of our habits and not decisions, so once the correct habits are in place, you will automatically perform those tasks on a day-to-day basis.
我们的日常行为几乎有一半属于习惯，而不是决定，所以一旦正确的习惯确立起来，你每天就会自动完成那些任务。
The best way to create and stick to a habit is to have strong motivation.
养成并坚持一个习惯的最好方法是拥有强烈的动力。
It’s easier to change your habits to lose weight if you have a health issue and you want to be around longer for your kids, or to grow your business if it is something you’re passionate about.
如果你有健康问题，又想为了孩子多活些年，那么改变习惯来减肥就会更容易；如果你热爱自己的事业，那么改变习惯来发展事业也会更容易。
Having a valuable outcome associated with a habit will help you stick to that habit permanently.
让一个习惯与某种有价值的结果联系在一起，会帮助你把这个习惯永久地坚持下去。
The art of self-control is one that most successful individuals have mastered.
自我控制这门艺术，大多数成功人士都已经掌握了。
Self-control enables you to avoid behaviors that don’t contribute to your success and adopt those that do.
自我控制能让你避免那些无助于成功的行为，并采取那些有助于成功的做法。
Because there is a delayed satisfaction associated with self-control, it can be easy to get off track.
由于与自我控制相伴的满足感要延迟到来，人可能很容易偏离正轨。
However, if you work on sticking to those small positive habits one day at a time, it becomes easier to stay strong and achieve that delayed reward.
不过，如果你努力一天一天地坚持那些小小的积极习惯，保持坚定、获得那份延迟的回报就会变得更容易。
Once a reward is achieved, it is much easier to continue sticking to your habits.
一旦获得了回报，继续坚持习惯就会容易得多。